Ahmed Eid Abd El-Hady

E-mail: ahmedzidan757@gmail.com Website: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ahmed-

eid-58b770158/

Phone: 01093854907 Address: Cairo

Nasr City

Summary

I am a **Full Stack Java Developer** with more than one year of experience at **IT - BLOCKS** Company Experienced Java Developer focused on solving customer problems, improving usability and maximizing efficiency. Specializing in creating Web applications.

Education

Computer Science

Sep 2011 — Jun 2015

Jun 2019 — 2020

Computers and Informatics Zagazig University

Degree: Good

Work experience

It-Blocks

Java Developer

<u>Ministry of Foreign Affairs:</u> (live) <u>& South Sinai Governorate:</u> (live)

& Bank De Cairo: (live)

It is a system on **CMS =>** correspondence system within the Ministry of Foreign Affairs to register correspondence issued and received from various sites, whether correspondence registered from the ministry or from any party outside it and registered inside ministry.

Technology

- View (jsp & servlet, javascript, jquery, ajax)
- Model(hibernate)
- Control(business javaEE, webservices restfull api)

It-Blocks Jan 2020 — 2020

Java Developer

Ministry of Interior, General Department for Passports, Immigration and Nationality: (live)

<u>&Egyptian Drug Authority:</u> (under development)

It is a system on **REQUESTS =>** The citizen sends his or her request, whether for immigration, acquisition of nationality, or the disposal of nationality from the salvage of the ministry's website, and the system converts it to correspondence to confirm the request from the state's security, or from the organization and administration or other relevant authorities, and then prints the application according to the special form Out and shape the model

<u>Technology</u>

View (jsp & servlet, javascript, jquery, ajax)

Abmed Fid Abd FL-Hady

- Model(hibernate)
- Control(business javaEE, webservices restfull api)

freelance

Feb 2020 — Jun 2020

Full Stack Java Developer

GYM: live in 2 GYM

About GYM we have admin user witch can add player, (player have subtype one of half-month or monthly)this pro deployed on tomcat

Technology

- View (Angular 9)
- Model(hibernate)
- Control(Spring Boot rest API, webservices restfull api)

It-Blocks

Feb 2020 — 2020

Java Developer

PDF Viewer: live in IT-Blocks Company

a PDF viewer to manipulate a pdf file, PDFviewer can allow user to annotate,add signature as image or pencil signature, add any new image and save or print it's document

Technology

HTML5, CSS3, Javascript and some plugin

freelance

Jun 2021 — under development

Full stack java developer

Store System (ABSystem): (under development)

A system specially available for contracting and construction companies, and it is a system that exists in the work environment and is used by warehouse keepers to organize warehouse work and offer to employers

Technology

- View (Angular 9)Model(hibernate)
- Control(Spring Boot rest API, webservices restfull api)

Qualifications

- <u>Database:</u> SQL Server ,MySQL ,Oracle 11g ,MongoDB
- Backend Developer: JavaEE ,JavaSE ,Hibernate ,Web Services ,Spring Boot ,JSP Servlet.
- <u>UI Developer:</u> Angular8 ,HTML5 ,CSS3 ,Javascript ,Typescript ,Bootstrap ,JQuery ,Ajax.
- IDE: NetBeans ,Eclipse.

Ahmed Eid Abd El-Hady 2